William Asadorian Collection TAM.461
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Ephemera: New York, undated (Box 17, Folder 127)
- Ephemera: Harson's New York Hathouse, undated (Box 17, Folder 128)
- Ephemera: World War I, early 20th century (Box 17, Folder 129)
- Photograph: New York City Journal and Courier Newspaper with Staff, circa 1880 (Box 17, Folder 130)
- Ephemera: Maspeth Steam Fire Engine Company No. 4 (Queens, New York), 1890 (Box 17, Folder 131)
- Correspondence: Sabbath, 1841 (Box 17, Folder 132)
- Correspondence: To David Kenney, Wall St., New York, 1845 (Box 17, Folder 133)
- Correspondence: Fragments of Annapolis Planation Letter, 1765 (Box 17, Folder 134)
- Receipt, 1827 (Box 17, Folder 135)
- Correspondence, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 136)
- Ephemera, undated (Box 17, Folder 137)
- Receipt, 1818 (Box 17, Folder 138)
- Ephemera, 19th century (Box 17, Folder 139)
- Correspondence: Captain Joseph Palmer (New York), undated (Box 17, Folder 140)
- Correspondence: Sheldon Fish (New York), 1837 (Box 17, Folder 141)
- Contract, 1745 (Box 17, Folder 142)
- Correspondence: Hire of a Slave (Kentucky), 1845 (Box 17, Folder 143)
- Correspondence: Slavery (Virginia), 1852 (Box 17, Folder 144)
- Brooklyn Theater Programs and Performances, 1878-1891 (Box 17, Folder 145)
- Correspondence: Payne Family (New York), 1820-1859 (Box 17, Folder 146)
- Photographs: New Britain, Connecticut, 1950s (Box 17, Folder 147)
- Photographs: Amelia Earhart (Hawaii), Dec 1934 (Box 17, Folder 148)
- Postcards of New York City Landmarks, undated (Box 17, Folder 149)
- Bi-Centennial Celebration at Glen Cove, L. I., May 25, 1868 (Box 17, Folder 150)
- Bi-Centennial Celebration at Glen Cove, L. I., May 25, 1868 (Box 17, Folder 151)
- Scrapbook, undated (Box 17, Folder 152)
- Certificate of Indenture, 1815 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- G. I. Joe: The Voice of the Veteran, May 1946 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- PM, April 25, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Letters from England, 1829-1837 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Correspondence to John King of Pennsylvania, 1819-1845 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Unidentified Letter, 1830 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Report Card of Student at Dr. Fitch's Family School for Boys (Norwalk, CT), 1889 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Letter from Merchant in New Orleans to Merchant in New York, 1846 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Letter from [Harvey?] B. Hawley to Emily Hawley, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Letter from John (?) Serving in the United States Navy during the Occupation of Japan (includes Japanese currency and sketch of U.S. carrier, probably CV-10 USS Yorktown, in Tokyo Bay), September 1945 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Mounted Photograph of Queen Victoria, [1901] (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Letter to Sophie (?) from Private Paul H. [Badstuelner?], Company A 122nd Engineers, American Expeditionary Force, Jan 26, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Connecticut Petition to Congress to Clear Navigational Danger at Hellgate (New York City), undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Letter from Charles B. Custer, 1837 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Shipping Invoice, 1836 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Letter to James Craik, 1830 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Unidentified Letter, 1832 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- British Registered Letter Envelopes (one with wax seal), 1920s-1930s (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Unidentifed Letter (Princeton, NJ), 1847 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Letter to Nat Field, 1839 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Letter to James Craik, 1828 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Portrait Sketch, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Portrait Sketch, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Letter to James Craik, 1830 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Letter to James Craik, 1831 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Letter to James Craik, 1831 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Unidentifed Letter, 1824 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Unidentifed Fragment, 1835 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Letter to Robert [Wickliff?] of Lexington, KY, 1830 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Letter to [Lancer and Sloph?], Attorney's at Law, 1830 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Letter from James Slaughter to Mr. Buchanan, 1834 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Sworn Oath from Kentucky, 1847 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Purchase Order Sent to Richard M. Cogan (includes hand-drawn seal), 1860 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Unidentified Letter, 1841 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Letter to J. J. Canby, 1829 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Unidentifed Letter, 1831 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Unidentifed Letter, 1840 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Letter to James Craik, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Letter to J. J. Cable, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Unidentified Letter, 1848 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Unidentified Letter, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
- [Speech?], 1867 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Letter to James Craik, 1829 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Court Documents, 1815-1858 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Correspondence of K. F. Stebbins, 1891 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Envelope Fragment, 1837 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1815-1903 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Binder of Photographs of New York City, late 19th century-early 20th century (Box 20, Item 1)
- Binder of Photographs of New York City, late 19th century-early 20th century (Box 20, Item 2)
- Binder of Photographs of New York City, early 20th century (Box 20, Item 3)
- Table of Contents from Unknown Volume, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Commerce & Industry Association of New York: Labor Relations Bureau Special Bulletin, May 12, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Bay State Builder (Associated General Contractors of Massachusetts), Volume Six, Number Eight, Aug 1948 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Social Action, Apr 15, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- "Factors in Achieving Industrial Harmony" by Clark Kerr, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Commerce and Industry Association of New York Annual Report, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Two Pamphlets on Labor-Management Relations, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Bay State Builder (Associated General Contractors of Massachusetts), Volume Five, Number Four, Apr 1947 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Bay State Builder (Associated General Contractors of Massachusetts), Volume Five, Number Five, May 1947 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Bay State Builder (Associated General Contractors of Massachusetts), Volume Five, Number Six, Jun 1947 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Bay State Builder (Associated General Contractors of Massachusetts), Volume Five, Number Seven, Jul 1947 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Labor Report, Volume VI, Number 25, Dec 2, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Placard for Cole P. Wright's Candidacy for State Senate on the Democratic and Progressive Tickets, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Placard for A. H. G. Hardwicke's Candidacy for New York State Senate on the National Progressive Party Ticket, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Occupy Buffalo Flyers, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Lecture Schedule from the Management 132 Class at New York University's School of Commerce Finance and Accounts, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Guide to Successful Legal Research, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- "What to Do about the Labor Mess" by Sumner H. Slichter, Dec 1946 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Agreement between R. H. Macy & Co. and the United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, Local 1-S, May 10, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- "What Labor Wants" by Dave Beck, May 1947 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- "The Art of Collective Bargaining" by Oliver Hoyem, circa 1940s (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Advertisement for First Edition of Who's Who in Labor, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Operating under the Taft-Hartley Act: A Practical Handbook for Labor Relations and Personnel Executives (Commerce and Industry Association of New York), 1947 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Binder of Photographs of New York City Street Scenes, 1890s-1910s (Box 21)
- Binder of World War I Dispatches and Printed Ephemera, 1914-2000s (Box 21)
- 20th Congress, 1st Session: Secretary of State Transmitting an Abstract of American Seamen, 1828 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Carvalho Borges, Antônio Pedro de: Letter Regarding Autograph of Brazilian Emperor, 1878 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Colby, Ira: Correspondence, 1893-1895 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Earl, Caleb: Letter to J.H. Jimley, 1806 July 16 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Gold and Austin Rail Road Supplies: Advertisement, circa 1888 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Goodwin, Thomas: Correspondence to Family, 1802-1806 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Greenwich Township: Election Document, 1799 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Hickley, J.H.: Invoice, 1817 September 4 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Joralemon Street: Image, circa 1904 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Kropotkin, Peter: Handwritten Note, Cambridge, MA, 1901 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Lawrence, J.H: Letter to Daniel Hendrickson, 1794 March 20 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Lewis, Betty: Carriage Receipt, 1796 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Mackay, Robert: Letter from Individual in Chinese Legation Department Regarding Newspaper Article, 1901 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Mercer, Charles Fenton: Letter Regarding Sale of Land, 1816 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Middlesex County: Surveyors Document, 1818 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- National Progressive Convention Card, 1912 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Page Seed Company: Receipts, 1896-1955 (Box 22, Folder 17-22)
- Unidentified: Diary, 1905-1914 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
- Unidentified (document in Russian), 1823 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Landscape Prints and Portraits (9x7 inches), circa 1880s-1900s (Box 24, Folder 1-4, Box 25, Folder 1-2)
- Portraits (4x2.5 inches), circa 1880s-1900s (Box 25, Folder 3-5, Box 26, Folder 1-2)
- Portraits (6x4.25 inches), circa 1880s-1900s (Box 26, Folder 3-10)
- Small Landscape Prints, circa 1880s-1900s (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Postcards, 1900s-1910s (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
- Correspondence: Letters, Postcards, Telegrams: Edward Washington to Mildred Washington, 1945-1971; 1-11 folders (Box 27, Folder 1-11)
- Letters, Postcards, Photographs: Individual Portraits of Men and Women, WWII era planes and Men in Uniform, 1879-1955; 1-36 folders (Box 28, Folder 1-36)
- Magazines, Correspondence, and Ephemera: Letters from the US War Department, Sale Inquiries, Art Magazines in French, 1869-1970; 1-28 folders (Box 29, Folder 1-28)
- Bonds: Confederate States of America Bank, 1 one thousand dollars bond and 5 five hundred bonds, 1868-1894; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Scrapbook, undated; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Photographs, Ephemera, Postcards: Portraits of Men and Women, Picture Postcards of European Cities and Landscapes, Airline Ephemera from the 1950s, circa 1850s-1960s; 1-80 folders (Box 31, Folder 1-80)
- 2 Prints: "Hunting and Fishing" by Honore Daumier, undated; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Menu: Chelsea Chop House, 1951; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Print: woman's silhouette, undated; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Print: "La Rue des Tombeaux a Pompei", undated; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Sheet music: "America's Centennial March" by D. L. Downing, 1876; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 5)